aromaweb.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy | AromaWeb

AromaWeb, LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates the website located at the following URL: https://www.aromaweb.com (hereinafter referred to as the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal data and data when you use our Service.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

## Definitions

  * **Service**

Service is the https://www.aromaweb.com website operated by AromaWeb, LLC

  * **Personal Data**

Personal Data is data about a living individual that can be identified from data (or from other information that may come into our possession).

  * **Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either by your use of the Service or via the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

## Information Collection and Use

We collect different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * If you submit a form, you will be asked to provide personally identifying information such as your name and email address so that your request can be handled. You are not obligated to submit any forms in order to use the Service.

#### Usage Data

We may automatically collect information on how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service visited by your IP address, the time and date of the visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

AromaWeb does not directly implement cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service. However, AromaWeb does utilize AddThis and Google Analytics which may use cookies (see below for more information).

Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

## Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), AromaWeb, LLC legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

AromaWeb, LLC may process your Personal Data because:

  * You have provided it to us in a form and we must use it in order to respond to your request.
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it is not overridden by your rights
  * To comply with the law

## Retention of Data

AromaWeb, LLC will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

AromaWeb, LLC will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer periods.

## Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those of your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

AromaWeb, LLC will take all the steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure of Data

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, AromaWeb, LLC may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

AromaWeb, LLC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of AromaWeb, LLC
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data and Usage Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), provide the Service on our behalf, perform Service-related services or assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics and Social Tools

We may use third-party Service Providers, including AddThis Google Analytics, to monitor and analyse the use of our Service and provide social sharing tools.

  * **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

  * **AddThis**

AddThis is a toolset that allows visitors to easily share images on social media.

For more information on the privacy practices of AddThis, please visit the AddThis Privacy Policy web page: <https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/addthis-privacy-policy.html>

### Advertising

AromaWeb displays advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service. These ads are displayed directly by AromaWeb and are not integrated or disclosed to third party advertising services.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Service contains links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. However, if an individual under the age of 18 submits a form to AromaWeb, his/her name or other identifiable information may be disclosed to AromaWeb, depending upon what the child typed into the form. If you are a parent or guardian and you become aware that your child has contacted AromaWeb without your consent, please contact us and every effort will be made to remove any emails/forms that your child has sent.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by using our Contact Us area.
